Guide to the Consumer Reports. Advocacy records, 1927-2011 and undated RL.11780
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Statements, Comments, Testimonies, etc., 1954-2001 and undated; 3
  - 1976, 12
    - 7605012-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7605013-1. Nutritional advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605014-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605015-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605016-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605017-1. Advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7605018-1. Drained food weights, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606001-1. Health care costs, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7606002-1. Food industry, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7606003-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7606004-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7606005-1. Funerals, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606006-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606007-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606008-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606009-0. Telecommunications, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606010-2. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606011-1. Warranties, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7606012-1. Warranties, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7607001-1. Public utilities, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7607002-1. Lead-based paint, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7607003-1. Food industry, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7607004-0. Consumer protection, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7607005-0. Spackling compounds, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7607006-1. Credit, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7607007-1. Credit, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608001-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608002-1. Renting, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608003-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608004-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608005-1. Air transport, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608006-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608007-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608008-1. Licensing, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7608009-1. Lead-based paint, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608010-1. Lead-based paint, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608011-1. Cigarette lighters, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7608012-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7609001-1. Credit, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609002-1. Lead-based paint, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7609003-1. Lead-based paint, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609004-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7609005-1. Antacids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609006-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609008-1. Public utilities, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609009-1. Oil industry, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609010-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609011-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7609012-1. Gasoline, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609013-1. Public utilities, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609014-1. Eye care, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7609015-1. Health care costs, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610001-1. Funerals, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610002-1. Food advertising, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610003-1. Meat industry, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610004-1. Oil industry, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7610005-1. Oil industry, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7610006-1. Natural gas, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610007-1. Natural gas, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610008-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610009-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610010-1. Cosmetics, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610011-1. Oil industry, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610012-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7610013-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611001-1. Air transport, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611002-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611003-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611004-1. Consumer participation, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611005-1. Oil industry, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611006-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611007-1. Antacids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611008-1. Antacids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611009-2. California public schools, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611010-1. Home ownership, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611011-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611012-2. Alcoholic beverages, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7611013-0. Physicians' services, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612001-2. Taxi services, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612002-2. Taxi services, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612003-1. Antacids, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612004-1. Estrogen, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612005-1. Business, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 7612006-1. Lawyers, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7612007-1. Licensing, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7612008-1. Licensing, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612009-1. Laboratory practices, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612010-2. Dairy products, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612011-0. Appliances, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612012-2. Toys, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612013-2. Toys, 1976 (Box 8)
    - 7612014-2. Toys, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 7612015-1. Banks, 1976 (Box 8)
  - 1977, 13
    - 7701001-1. Potatoes, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701002-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701003-1. Aerosols, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701004-1. Baby food, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701005-1. Lead-based paint, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701006-1. Lawyers, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701007-1. Antacids, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701008-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701009-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701010-2. Alcoholic beverages, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7701011-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7702001-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7702002-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7702003-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7702004-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7702005-1. Licensing, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7702007-2. Alcoholic beverages, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7703001-1. Life insurance, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7703002-1. Laetrile, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703003-1. Lead-based paint, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703004-1. Hospitals, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703005-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703006-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703007-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7703008-1. Life insurance, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703009-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703010-1. Health care costs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703011-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703012-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703013-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7703014-1. Footwear, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703015-1. Life insurance, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703016-0. Footwear, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703017-1. Laboratory practices, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703018-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703019-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703020-1. Class actions, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703021-1. Standards, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7703022-1. Standards, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704001-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704002-1. Food pricing, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704003-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704004-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704005-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704006-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704007-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704008-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7704009-1. Class actions, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7704010-1. Standards, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705001-1. Debt collection, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705002-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705003-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705004-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705005-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705006-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705007-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705008-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705009-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705010-1. Renting, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705011-2. Coffee, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7705012-2. Coffee, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705013-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705014-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705015-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705016-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7705017-1. Standards, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706001-2. Taxi services, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706002-2. Taxi services, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706003-2. Taxi services, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706004-1. Saccharine, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706005-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706006-1. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706007-0. Lawn mowers, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706008-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7706009-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706010-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706011-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706012-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7706013-1. Cable television, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7707001-2. Taxi services, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7707002-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7707003-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7707004-2. Textbooks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7707005-2. Cereals, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708001-0. Lawn mowers, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708002-1. Peas, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708003-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708004-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708005-1. Insulation, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708006-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708007-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708008-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708009-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708010-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708011-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708012-2. Lawyers, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708013-1. Natural gas, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708014-1. Consumer information services, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7708015-2. Textbooks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709001-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7709002-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709003-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709004-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709005-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709006-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709007-2. Alcoholic beverages, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709008-2. Prescription drugs, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7709009-2. Prescription drugs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709010-1. Alcoholic beverages, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709011-1. Weights and measures, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709012-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7709013-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710001-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7710002-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7710003-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710004-0. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710005-0. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710006-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7710007-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7710008-0. Cable television, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710009-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710010-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710011-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710012-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710013-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710014-1. Oil industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710015-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710016-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710017-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7710018-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711001-0. Televisions, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711002-1. Cable television, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711003-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 17)
    - 7711004-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711005-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711006-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711007-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711008-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711009-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7711010-0. School lunch programs, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712001-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712002-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712003-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712004-1. Product hazards, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712005-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712006-1. Credit, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712007-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712008-1. Meat industry, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712009-1. Banks, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712010-1. Air transport, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712011-1. Consumer participation, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712012-1. Bread, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712013-2. Dairy products, 1977 (Box 8)
    - 7712014-0. Television advertising to children, 1977 (Box 8)
  - 1978, 14
    - 7801001-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801002-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801003-1. Potatoes, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801004-1. Insulation, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801005-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801006-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801007-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7801008-1. Meat industry, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801009-2. Carrots, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801010-2. Employment, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7801011-2. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7801012-1. Product liability, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802001-1. Automobile insurance, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802002-1. Appliances, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802003-0. Tin, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802004-1. Federal Reserve Board, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802005-2. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802006-2. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7802007-2. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803001-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803002-1. Air transport, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803003-1. Meat industry, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803004-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803005-1. Food weights, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803006-1. Meat industry, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803007-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803008-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803009-1. Automobile servicing, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803010-1. Cable television, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803011-1. Food weights, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803012-1. Credit cards, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803013-0. Lawn mowers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7803014-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7804001-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804002-1. Class actions, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7804003-1. Oil industry, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7804004-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804005-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804006-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804007-1. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7804008-1. Air transport, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804009-2. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 8)
    - 7804010-2. Patients' rights, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804011-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804012-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804013-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804014-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804015-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7804016-2. Patients' rights, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805001-1. Radiation, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805002-1. Telecommunications, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805003-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805004-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805005-1. Product liability, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805006-1. Automobile insurance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805007-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805008-1. Telecommunications, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805009-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805010-1. Air transport, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805011-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805012-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805013-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805014-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805015-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805016-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805017-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805018-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7805019-2. Patients' rights, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805020-2. Patients' rights, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805021-2. Petitioning, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805022-2. Alcoholic beverages, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805023-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805024-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805025-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805026-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805027-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805028-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805029-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805030-2. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7805031-1. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806001-1. Life insurance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806002-1. Automobile insurance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806003-1. International trade, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806004-1. Radio broadcasting, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806005-1. Toxic Substances Control Act, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806006-1. Microwave ovens, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806007-1. Cable television, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7806008-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7806009-2. Insurance, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7806010-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7807001-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7807002-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7807003-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7807004-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7807005-1. Life insurance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7807006-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7807007-1. Business, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7807008-2. Conflict of interest, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808001-1. Banks, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808002-1. Business, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808003-1. Food standards, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808004-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808005-2. Taxi services, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7808006-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809001-1. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809002-1. Appliances, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809003-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809004-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7809005-1. Meat industry, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809006-1. Hearing aids, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809007-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7809008-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7809009-1. Life insurance, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7809010-1. Life insurance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7810001-0. Food weights, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7810002-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7810003-2. Food labeling, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7810004-1. Mortgages, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811001-1. Consumer participation, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811002-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811003-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811004-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811005-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811006-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811007-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7811008-1. Lawn mowers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811009-1. Air transport, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811010-1. Standards, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811011-0. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811012-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811013-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811014-1. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7811015-1. Television advertising to children, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812001-1. International trade, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812002-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812003-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812004-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812005-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812006-1. Credit, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812007-1. Life insurance, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812008-1. Automobile tires, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812009-1. Food weights, 1978 (Box 17)
    - 7812010-1. Lawyers, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812011-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812012-0. School lunch programs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - 7812013-1. Washington Office activity report, 1978 (Box 9)
  - 1979, 15
    - 7901001-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7901002-1. Pesticides, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7901003-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7901004-2. Real estate, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7901005-1. Pesticides, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7901006-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7902001-1. Insurance, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7902002-1. Antitrust, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7902003-3. Product liability, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7902004-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7902005-4. Insurance, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903001-2. Dairy products, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903002-3. Product liability, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7903003-3. Funerals, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903004-3. Consumer fraud, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903005-3. Prescription drugs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903006-1. Product liability, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903007-0. OTC (over the counter) drugs, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7903008-1. Standards, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903009-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7903010-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903011-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903012-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7903013-1. Lawn mowers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903014-1. Lawn mowers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903015-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903016-2. Advertising, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903017-0. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7903018-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904001-0. Televisions, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904002-1. International trade, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7904003-0. Mortgages, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904004-1. Microwave ovens, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904005-1. Lawn mowers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904006-0. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904007-1. Telecommunications, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7904008-1. Telecommunications, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7904009-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7904010-0. CU legislative priorities for 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905001-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905002-1. Moving industry, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905003-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905004-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905005-1. Life insurance, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905006-1. Product liability, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905007-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905008-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7905009-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905010-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905011-2. Television advertising to children, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905012-1. Life insurance, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7905013-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906001-2. Television advertising to children, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906002-0. Education, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906003-1. Product liability, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906004-1. Moving industry, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7906005-1. Banks, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906006-1. Consumer participation, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906007-1. International trade, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7906008-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7906009-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7906010-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7906011-1. Consumer complaints arbitration, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7907001-2. Television advertising to children, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907002-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7907003-1. Automobile warranties, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7907004-1. Meat industry, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907005-1. Meat industry, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907006-3. Public utilities, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907007-3. Telecommunications, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907008-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907009-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7907010-1. Real estate, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908001-2. Mental health, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908002-1. Moving industry, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908003-3. Public utilities, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908004-1. Antitrust, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908005-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908006-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908007-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7908008-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909001-2. Television advertising to children, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909002-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909003-0. Gas-saving devices, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909004-1. Beverages, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909005-1. Federal Trade Commission, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909006-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909007-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909008-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909009-2. Food crisis, 1979 (Box 17)
    - 7909010-1. Televisions, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909011-0. Insurance, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909012-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909013-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7909014-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910001-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7910002-0. Toxic Substances Strategic Committee, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910003-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910004-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7910005-1. Moving industry, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910006-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7910007-1. Telecommunications, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910008-1. Gasoline, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910009-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910010-1. Real estate, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7910011-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911001-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7911002-1. Life insurance, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7911003-1. Lawn mowers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911004-1. Credit, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7911005-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7911006-1. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911007-0. Fluoridation, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911008-2. Lawyers, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911009-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911010-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7911011-1. Life insurance, 1979 (Box 18)
    - 7911012-1. Pesticides, 1979 (Box 9)
    - 7912001-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 10)
    - 7912002-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 10)
    - 7912003-0. School lunch programs, 1979 (Box 10)
    - 7912004-1. Employment, 1979 (Box 10)
  - 1980, 16
    - 8000001-2. Getting Action: How to Petition State Government, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8001001-2. Housing, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8001002-1. Lawyers, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8001003-1. Lawn mowers, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8001004-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8001005-0. School lunch programs, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8002001-0. Solar energy, 1980 (Box 10)
    - 8002002-3. Natural gas, 1980 (Box 10)